soapzone.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Statement

###  Privacy Statement for SoapZone.com 

**SoapZone.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: [ SoapZone.com ](http://soapzone.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and to roughly estimate the number of unique visitors to the site over various time periods. 

We use your browser's identification string (such as `Mozilla/4.7 (Macintosh; I; PPC)`) to help diagnose problems with page designs and coding. 

####  Cookies 

Our site uses cookies to store member preferences input by members in certain forms, including the Chat Options panel in the Frame Chat interface, and to keep track of recent searches on the Search pages. 

####  Advertisers 

SoapZone.com works with third parties that serve ads to this site. 

Ads delivered on SoapZone.com may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our web site, cookies received with advertising are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. Likewise, our ad companies do not have access to cookies generated and accessed by SoapZone.com. 

**GOOGLE advertising:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**BURST MEDIA advertising:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information, including their name and email address. 

Contact information from the registration form is used to get in touch with the member when necessary. Contact information is not given, leased, rented, or sold to advertisers or other third parties. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **SoapZone.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

When a member sends email to another member using the Send Email form (available from the message boards), the sender's email address is disclosed to the recipient. SoapZone.com does not disclose the recipient's address to the sender. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

The member database is password-protected and the password list is encrypted. The only party with access to member information is the site owner, Jeff Jungblut. 

###  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can use the feedback form at: <http://soapzone.com/doc/webmasterfeedback.html>

Or write to us at:

JEFF JUNGBLUT  
SOAPZONE.COM  
PO BOX 211585  
CHULA VISTA, CA 92121-1585
